Matt Lucas

Summary

San Francisco Bay Area Senior Email Developer with nine years experience in digital marketing. Extensive, hands-on experience with coding responsive HTML emails and digital marketing assets for clients such as Intel and Autodesk, as well as building automated marketing campaigns in Marketo, Eloqua and Pardot.

Experience

Email Marketing Developer / PubNub

AUGUST 2016 - PRESENT / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Senior Email Developer / Pierry Software

MAY 2016 - JULY 2016 / REDWOOD CITY, CA

Client Work: NetJets, San Jose Earthquakes, IMAX, Postmates, Uber

Digital Marketing Engineer / Teradata Interactive

MAY 2014 - APRIL 2016 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: Procter & Gamble, Autodesk, Intel, Hertz, 7-Eleven, Brocade

HTML Production Engineer / Ozone Online

SEPTEMBER 2013 - MAY 2014 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: Brocade, Intel, Medtronic, JPMorgan Chase & Co., Autodesk

Web Producer / OpenMarketing

DECEMBER 2012 - JUNE 2013 / SAN FRANCISCO, CA

Client Work: PresenceLearning, Social Fluency, LiveHive, Kriste Michelini Interiors

Contact

510-318-4985 mattdavidlucas@gmail.com mattdavidlucas.com linkedin.com/in/mattdavidlucas

Marketing Platforms

Marketo

Eloqua

Pardot

Salesforce Marketing Cloud (ExactTarget)
Teradata Marketing Applications

Dev/Production Skills

Responsive HTML Email Development

Marketing Automation

Adobe Photoshop CC

HTML

CSS & Sass

JavaScript & jQuery

PHP

Linux Command Line

Education & Certifications

California College of the Arts

Bachelor of Fine Arts, 2003 - 2007

Salesforce Marketing Cloud & Marketo Certified

Web Production & Design Manager / Bulldog Reporter

JANUARY 2010 - DECEMBER 2012 / OAKLAND, CA